BADAR UDDIN TARIQ

WEB APPLICATION DEVELOPER

T: (+971) 50 2054647 E: badar.tariq17@gmail.com

Dear Sir/Madam:

I wish to apply for a job in your company. Along with my acadamics qualification, I have strong interest in pursuing a career in your administration.

My background included **2.5 years** of experience in application development. I have worked as **Web Developer at ZaraMobility/Level3BOS.** I have served my services to the forum with full **enthusiasm,dedication** and **loyalty**.

In addition to the experience, I have gained strong communication skills and ability to solve issues and manage things in appropriate ways. I am also a knowledge seeker of new technologies to inhance my work and to inovate my work effectively. My expertise is on PHP framework Laravel, Bootstrap and Javascript.

I am confident to say that i can serve good services to your company and will complete my duty with full dedication. I assure you that my presence will proved to be beneficial to the company. I look forward for your response to my application for the job. Please see the accompanying resume for details of my experience and education.

Thankyou for your considration.

Sincerely, Badar Uddin Tariq

BADAR UDDIN TARIQ

WEB APPLICATION DEVELOPER

T: (+971) 50 2054647 E: badar.tariq17@gmail.com

ABOUT ME

A multi-skilled and experienced application developer with an extensive track record of developing and maintaining high-quality software solutions

EDUCATION

2013 - 2017 DADABHOUY INSTITUTE OF HIGHER EDUCATION BS (COMPUTER SCIENCE)

2016

(IBA) INSTITUTE OF BUSINESS ADMINISTRATION

CERTIFICATE PHP PROGRAMMING

2009 - 2012 GOVT. ALLAMA IQBAL COLLEGE INTERMEDIATE

SKILLS

HTML	•	•	•	•	•
CSS	•	•	•	•	•
PHP	•	•	•	•	•
LARAVEL	•	•	•		•
JAVA SCRIPT	•	•	•	•	•
MY SQL	•	•	•	•	•
JQUERY	•	•	•	•	•
BOOTSTRAP	•	•	•	•	•

EXPERIENCES

WEB DEVELOPER ZARA MOBILITY SERVICES LEVEL3BOS

JAN 2018 PRESENT

Working as a WEB DEVEOPER TO Develop of new portals, maintenance & error fixing on live portals, managing complete live database, managing operational support for employees.

INTERN ENGINEER **DIGIVERKZ**

JAN 2017 TO FEB 2017

On different projects of companies my job responsibility to complete tasks in designated time. This role is totally provided an experience in PHP.

INTERN ENGINEER IKODE STUDIO

JAN 2016 TO MAY 2016

IKODE studio is one of renown software house which provide PHP core software supports to their clients. My job responsibilities is to did coding in C# for different applications.

PROJECTS

MOBILELINK SUPPLIES

□ www.mobilelinkusa.com/spl

MOBILYLLC EWR EMPLOYEE WEEKLY REPORT

□ www.mobilyllc.com/ewr

MYVITAL WIRELESS CALLING TREE

 $\ \ \, \square \ \, www.myvitalwireless.com/callingtree$

LEVEL3BOS ELS EMPLOYEE LEAVE SYSTEM

□ www.level3bos.com/els

MOBILELINK TM CHECKLIST

□ www.mobilelinkusa.com/tm-checklist

MOBILELINK EMS EVENT MANAGEMENT SYSTEM

□ www.mobilelinkusa.com/ems

MOBILELINK TIME CORRECTION

□ www.mobilelinkusa.com/tcorrection

LEVEL3BOS PAYROLL

□ www.level3bos.com/payroll

MOBILYLLC STATUS CHANGE FORM

□ www.mobilyllc.com/hrscf